[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Did he have a point?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "have", "a", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Is he right as an elected official to stick rigidly to those parameters or not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "as", "an", "elected", "official", "to", "stick", "rigidly", "to", "those", "parameters", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "You know, I know what all the buttons of an airplane do.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "know", "what", "all", "the", "buttons", "of", "an", "airplane", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "And for the wider country, by the weekend, is everything beginning to get back to some kind of normality?", "question_tokens": ["And", "for", "the", "wider", "country", ",", "by", "the", "weekend", ",", "is", "everything", "beginning", "to", "get", "back", "to", "some", "kind", "of", "normality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Slightly.", "answer_tokens": ["Slightly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["weekend"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["San Antonio"]}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "IN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "... what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["...", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I was actually listening to it here in San Antonio through the live feed that they provide and when he said that I was like -- I must have heard that wrong and realized I hadn't heard it wrong and this is the sense of this particular senator takes over and over and over again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "listening", "to", "it", "here", "in", "San", "Antonio", "through", "the", "live", "feed", "that", "they", "provide", "and", "when", "he", "said", "that", "I", "was", "like", "--", "I", "must", "have", "heard", "that", "wrong", "and", "realized", "I", "had", "n't", "heard", "it", "wrong", "and", "this", "is", "the", "sense", "of", "this", "particular", "senator", "takes", "over", "and", "over", "and", "over", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "What do you feel about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, it makes my heart pound for -- to hear that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "makes", "my", "heart", "pound", "for", "--", "to", "hear", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "What do you think can be done to try and change that mentality?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "can", "be", "done", "to", "try", "and", "change", "that", "mentality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What is your specific criticism of what they are doing in Denmark?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "specific", "criticism", "of", "what", "they", "are", "doing", "in", "Denmark", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, criticism, I couldn't even go beyond criticism.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "criticism", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "even", "go", "beyond", "criticism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Denmark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Is that the only way to try and control groups of animals in the wild or in the zoo?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "only", "way", "to", "try", "and", "control", "groups", "of", "animals", "in", "the", "wild", "or", "in", "the", "zoo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "But is that any argument that has any wanted to you at all about the way you control a group of perhaps predominantly male and female giraffe in that situation?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "that", "any", "argument", "that", "has", "any", "wanted", "to", "you", "at", "all", "about", "the", "way", "you", "control", "a", "group", "of", "perhaps", "predominantly", "male", "and", "female", "giraffe", "in", "that", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Why should the Danish frankly be able to treat giraffe's the way they wish too if they believe it's the right way to treat them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "the", "Danish", "frankly", "be", "able", "to", "treat", "giraffe", "'s", "the", "way", "they", "wish", "too", "if", "they", "believe", "it", "'s", "the", "right", "way", "to", "treat", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, I think you're raising a good point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "raising", "a", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "From your expertise, is that I am right, are certain animals able to deal with being in zoos better than others and should there be restrictions dependent on that?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "expertise", ",", "is", "that", "I", "am", "right", ",", "are", "certain", "animals", "able", "to", "deal", "with", "being", "in", "zoos", "better", "than", "others", "and", "should", "there", "be", "restrictions", "dependent", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I would say, in the older days obviously we had our problems.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", ",", "in", "the", "older", "days", "obviously", "we", "had", "our", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What the hell is going through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["What", "the", "hell", "is", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I didn't even know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "even", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "I would imagine the pleasure factor diminishes quite quickly, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "imagine", "the", "pleasure", "factor", "diminishes", "quite", "quickly", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I mean is -- I still enjoy doing it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "--", "I", "still", "enjoy", "doing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What makes you guys go out there and risk death?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "you", "guys", "go", "out", "there", "and", "risk", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Not everyday is like that obviously, but it's just the whole another world you're just by yourself, I mean, just you and the machine and you're trying everything not to get stuck and just keep your thrill way up.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "everyday", "is", "like", "that", "obviously", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "just", "the", "whole", "another", "world", "you", "'re", "just", "by", "yourself", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "just", "you", "and", "the", "machine", "and", "you", "'re", "trying", "everything", "not", "to", "get", "stuck", "and", "just", "keep", "your", "thrill", "way", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Did you think you are going to survived it or what happens to you in your head?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "you", "are", "going", "to", "survived", "it", "or", "what", "happens", "to", "you", "in", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, like -- I've seen a little bit of like what I thought was a rooster from another snowmobile.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "like", "--", "I", "'ve", "seen", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "like", "what", "I", "thought", "was", "a", "rooster", "from", "another", "snowmobile", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "But do you think on serious point there should be some form of regulations for snowmobiling?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "on", "serious", "point", "there", "should", "be", "some", "form", "of", "regulations", "for", "snowmobiling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I mean -- and there is a -- to a certain extent a form regulation like there's areas we can't go.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "--", "and", "there", "is", "a", "--", "to", "a", "certain", "extent", "a", "form", "regulation", "like", "there", "'s", "areas", "we", "ca", "n't", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Do you basically have to have a screw loose to be doing this snowmobiling a lot?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "basically", "have", "to", "have", "a", "screw", "loose", "to", "be", "doing", "this", "snowmobiling", "a", "lot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I mean there's a lot of different of styles of it I guess.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "different", "of", "styles", "of", "it", "I", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "So that's a yes basically, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "'s", "a", "yes", "basically", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Yes, and there's way crazier people than me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "there", "'s", "way", "crazier", "people", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary resurgence?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "this", "extraordinary", "resurgence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "It doesn't feel surreal I mean it feels very real it's happening, and I understand what's happening, I'm aware of what's happening.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "feel", "surreal", "I", "mean", "it", "feels", "very", "real", "it", "'s", "happening", ",", "and", "I", "understand", "what", "'s", "happening", ",", "I", "'m", "aware", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Is that the culmination of everything you've ever work for or do you believe in a way it maybe the start of something very special?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "culmination", "of", "everything", "you", "'ve", "ever", "work", "for", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "in", "a", "way", "it", "maybe", "the", "start", "of", "something", "very", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I think it's a wonderful moment in my career that is in the middle of its approach.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "wonderful", "moment", "in", "my", "career", "that", "is", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "its", "approach", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "I tweeted the other day, are you on Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["I", "tweeted", "the", "other", "day", ",", "are", "you", "on", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Is that the key?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "key", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "That's -- yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Who are the key people when you look back over the whole time that you would feel most thankful to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "key", "people", "when", "you", "look", "back", "over", "the", "whole", "time", "that", "you", "would", "feel", "most", "thankful", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, I've got thanks -- I've got my own personal thanks to God, I've got my own personal thanks to family in many respects, the family I've got now, the family I came from, and I've got another little secret thank for somebody I know very well that I might share if I was so fortunate to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "thanks", "--", "I", "'ve", "got", "my", "own", "personal", "thanks", "to", "God", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "my", "own", "personal", "thanks", "to", "family", "in", "many", "respects", ",", "the", "family", "I", "'ve", "got", "now", ",", "the", "family", "I", "came", "from", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "got", "another", "little", "secret", "thank", "for", "somebody", "I", "know", "very", "well", "that", "I", "might", "share", "if", "I", "was", "so", "fortunate", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What do you think you'll feel when you're standing there if you get that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "feel", "when", "you", "'re", "standing", "there", "if", "you", "get", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm -- look, I'm not there yet so ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "--", "look", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "there", "yet", "so", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "But if you do, how would you feel?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "do", ",", "how", "would", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "... I really haven't thought about what I would feel.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "I", "really", "have", "n't", "thought", "about", "what", "I", "would", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Replay that -- just any moment?", "question_tokens": ["Replay", "that", "--", "just", "any", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Any moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "The greatest moment?", "question_tokens": ["The", "greatest", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "One you'd most like to live through again.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "you", "'d", "most", "like", "to", "live", "through", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "What impact did that have on you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "impact", "did", "that", "have", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Courage, integrity, you know, anybody loses a father that's the main crutch in a man's life, and he's there for a reason because, you know, if it ever comes down to it you got, you know, my father would lean up against me.", "answer_tokens": ["Courage", ",", "integrity", ",", "you", "know", ",", "anybody", "loses", "a", "father", "that", "'s", "the", "main", "crutch", "in", "a", "man", "'s", "life", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "there", "for", "a", "reason", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "it", "ever", "comes", "down", "to", "it", "you", "got", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "father", "would", "lean", "up", "against", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "So what's your father have made of you being Oscar nominee?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "your", "father", "have", "made", "of", "you", "being", "Oscar", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "He'd love it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'d", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Can you quite believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}, "docId": "140213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "How I can lose 43 pounds quickly?", "question_tokens": ["How", "I", "can", "lose", "43", "pounds", "quickly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Go to Mexico and drink the water.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "to", "Mexico", "and", "drink", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]